<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DayEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns="urn:newtelligence-com:dasblog:runtime:data">
  <Date>2008-06-08T17:00:00-07:00</Date>
  <Entries>
    <Entry>
      <Content>&lt;div class="ExternalClassFF8309F833B5442F808BE4FF668FE52C"&gt;   &lt;div class="ExternalClass77A8144EBF694F24980B7BAE0CF6737B"&gt;     &lt;div&gt;       &lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Calibri" size="3"&gt;Our mission this weekend was to put up the permanent wood foundation walls. Those walls need to be built before the concrete pad can be poured. If we don&amp;#8217;t get the walls finished our entire schedule will be thrown off by 3 days or so. With this in mind I snuck off work at 2:30 on Friday and drove straight to the land. Traffic wasn&amp;#8217;t being agreeable so the 2.5 hour trip ended up taking 5 hours. Once I arrived I spent the remaining 2 hours of light getting two more pieces of the foundation wall up. Since I had forgotten both a spoon and can opener my dinner consisted of a granola bar instead of SpaghettiO&amp;#8217;s as originally planned.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Calibri" size="3"&gt;It had rained all day on Friday and was supposed to do the same for Saturday, but luckily it was just overcast all day. I got up at 8:30 or so, ate another granola bar, and proceeded to put up another 3 wall sections before realizing the measurements had to be wrong. After studying the plans I realized I was supposed to be measuring 20 feet 7/8&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; inches to the outside corner of the walls, not the inside. By the time I fixed the first two wall sections Mike and Sara arrived with a trailer full of food for our two week stay next weekend. More importantly, they also arrived with a Subway sub for me. After mounting the stop-motion web cam on the roof of the shed, we got to work. We spent the rest of the day Saturday putting up walls and finished with just the back extension left to go. Dinner was Phad Thai and curried rice.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://dome.msn2.net/content/binary/WindowsLiveWriter/Soresorehands_13610/FoundationASsembly2_2.jpg"&gt;&lt;img style="border-right: 0px; border-top: 0px; border-left: 0px; border-bottom: 0px" height="359" alt="FoundationASsembly2" src="http://dome.msn2.net/content/binary/WindowsLiveWriter/Soresorehands_13610/FoundationASsembly2_thumb.jpg" width="536" border="0" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;        &lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Calibri" size="3"&gt;On Sunday we got the back extension finished after a lot of measuring to make sure it was square. We also had to dig out another corner to leave room for the weeping tile and gravel drainage. While we were doing that the concrete contractor showed up to review the job. He didn&amp;#8217;t foresee any obstacles and the slab will be poured on Friday. When the last walls were in their correct place we went around and put three bolts in each intersection as well as half a tube of glue. Since it was getting late we didn&amp;#8217;t get a chance to put the additional top plate on all the walls, but that can wait until next week. Breakfast was an egg and cheese omelet and lunch was a roll with butter.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://dome.msn2.net/content/binary/WindowsLiveWriter/Soresorehands_13610/FoundationASsembly3_2.jpg"&gt;&lt;img style="border-right: 0px; border-top: 0px; border-left: 0px; border-bottom: 0px" height="363" alt="FoundationASsembly3" src="http://dome.msn2.net/content/binary/WindowsLiveWriter/Soresorehands_13610/FoundationASsembly3_thumb.jpg" width="542" border="0" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;     &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</Content>
      <Created>2008-06-09T03:00:38-07:00</Created>
      <Modified>2008-07-02T22:06:33.828125-07:00</Modified>
      <EntryId>79ed120c-dade-403c-9dd4-a60944d7cda4</EntryId>
      <Description />
      <Title>Sore, sore hands</Title>
      <Categories />
      <Author>neil</Author>
      <IsPublic>true</IsPublic>
      <Syndicated>true</Syndicated>
      <ShowOnFrontPage>true</ShowOnFrontPage>
      <AllowComments>true</AllowComments>
      <Attachments />
      <Crossposts />
      <Latitude xsi:nil="true" />
      <Longitude xsi:nil="true" />
    </Entry>
    <Entry>
      <Content>&lt;div class="ExternalClassADB161394B9541C299DD35CB916624DC"&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe style="width: 500px; height: 375px" src="http://silverlight.services.live.com/invoke/66324/Dome%20Foundation%20Day%202/iframe.html" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://silverlight.services.live.com/66324/Dome%20Foundation%20Day%202/video.wmv"&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt; (15mb)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;</Content>
      <Created>2008-06-08T19:00:52-07:00</Created>
      <Modified>2008-07-04T10:53:51.453125-07:00</Modified>
      <EntryId>24bb1bd9-54d6-4a06-ae94-4f89ccc1ec14</EntryId>
      <Description />
      <Title>June 8th Foundation Assembly Video</Title>
      <Categories>Videos</Categories>
      <Author>mike</Author>
      <IsPublic>true</IsPublic>
      <Syndicated>true</Syndicated>
      <ShowOnFrontPage>true</ShowOnFrontPage>
      <AllowComments>true</AllowComments>
      <Attachments />
      <Crossposts />
      <Latitude xsi:nil="true" />
      <Longitude xsi:nil="true" />
    </Entry>
  </Entries>
</DayEntry>